<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-10-23T06:38:58+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Anisha &amp;amp; Suharsh Blog</title><subtitle>Copyright © 2023 anishasuharsh.com</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Sri Vansantha Bhavan</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/south%20indian/2023/04/08/sri-vasantha-bhavan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sri Vansantha Bhavan" /><published>2023-04-08T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-08T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/south%20indian/2023/04/08/sri-vasantha-bhavan</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/south%20indian/2023/04/08/sri-vasantha-bhavan.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Boxed Lunch - Bisibelabath</li>
  <li>Vasantha Bhavan Thali</li>
  <li>Filter Coffee</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Sri Vasantha Bhavan is an excellent choice for a low-key South Indian eatery in the East Bay.</p>

<p>The food was fresh, flavorful, and seemed to use high-quality ingredients. It was clear the owner took pride in the options they had to offer. We offhand mentioned that
we didn’t want sweets in our Thalis and he went out of the way to offer many other things we could substitute.</p>

<p>Compared to other south indian eateries in the area, the value for the quantity of food was reasonable.</p>

<p>The ambiance is on par with most south indian places; loud clanging of pans, and lots of conversations going on. That being said, it was much less packed 
than some other joints (at least on a saturday afternoon).</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="South Indian" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Boxed Lunch - Bisibelabath Vasantha Bhavan Thali Filter Coffee]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Casa Lupe</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/mexican/2023/04/07/casa-lupe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Casa Lupe" /><published>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/mexican/2023/04/07/casa-lupe</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/mexican/2023/04/07/casa-lupe.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Vegetarian Chimichanga</li>
  <li>Cheese and Veggie Enchiladas</li>
  <li>Huevos Rancheros</li>
  <li>Guacamole Tostada</li>
  <li>Mexican Hot Chocolate</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Casa Lupe is our go-to Mexican sit-down restaurant. Its cozy feel and friendly service are what bring us back.</p>

<p>The staff has remained the same for the many years that we have come and seem to have a great relationship with all repeat diners.</p>

<p>Food is solid – both salsas are fresh and have some kick, the beans are flavorful, and portions are quite generous.</p>

<p>You can find better-tasting Mexican Food in the Bay Area, but on the whole, its hard to come by a better sit-down experience. Feels like family.</p>

<p>Pro-tip: if you like quacamole, get the Guacamole Tostada. The tostada comes completely smothered in guacamole and is an avocado lover’s dream.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="Mexican" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Vegetarian Chimichanga Cheese and Veggie Enchiladas Huevos Rancheros Guacamole Tostada Mexican Hot Chocolate]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cicero’s Pizza</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/pizza/2023/04/07/ciceros-pizza.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cicero’s Pizza" /><published>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/pizza/2023/04/07/ciceros-pizza</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/pizza/2023/04/07/ciceros-pizza.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Spicy Vegetarian Pizza</li>
  <li>Small Cheese Pizza</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Cicero’s is a great vegetarian pizza joint, that favors folks who love thin crust with spicy toppings.</p>

<p>The pizza is always consistent in taste and crispiness, and the tomatoes, onions, and jalapenos always feel fresh. The tomatoes surprisingly do not make the pizza soggy.</p>

<p>The price is on par with other popular pizza places in the area.</p>

<p>Ordering happens up front and they call your name when your pizza is ready. The interior is bustling (at least when it was open before COVID). Be prepared to wait, the pizza takes 25 min to make.</p>

<p>For takeout orders, be sure to call before 6pm to schedule your order as most of the time after 6:15 the line is always busy and you cannot get through.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="Pizza" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Spicy Vegetarian Pizza Small Cheese Pizza]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dusita Thai</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/thai/2023/04/07/dusita-thai.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dusita Thai" /><published>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/thai/2023/04/07/dusita-thai</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/thai/2023/04/07/dusita-thai.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Dusita’s Kao Soy – (request vegetarian)</li>
  <li>Basil Tofu &amp; Mixed Vegetables</li>
  <li>Green Papaya Salad</li>
  <li>Green Curry</li>
  <li>Basil Fried Rice</li>
  <li>Pad Kee Mao</li>
  <li>Pad Thai</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Dusita Thai is one of our favorite Thai restaurant, for only one reason – the food is consistently delicious. There is even a dedicated vegetarian menu!</p>

<p>It’s hard to come by Thai food that has so much flavor that even if you get them at low levels of spice, you feel no need to add any sauce to it to make it taste good.</p>

<p>That being said, Dusita’s food is spicy. If you ask for “medium” spice level, they’ll ask “have you tried our Medium before?”. For dishes like curries and stir-fries the spice scale is reasonable. But be warned – “medium” level Papaya Salad is very spicy!</p>

<p>Due to COVID, most of our experiences have been take out, so our Service score reflects this. Pickup orders take a long and sometimes unpredictable amount of time. Recently pickup time estimates seem to be more accurate, but still be prepared to wait up to 90 min for a dinner pickup order. Don’t even bother trying to call for a pickup order; you will either get no answer, an response with a 1 hour estimated wait, or once they just left the phone off the reciever after picking up.</p>

<p>Portions are reasonable and on par with the average Bay Area Thai eatery. The lunch combo value is exceptional though.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="Thai" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Dusita’s Kao Soy – (request vegetarian) Basil Tofu &amp; Mixed Vegetables Green Papaya Salad Green Curry Basil Fried Rice Pad Kee Mao Pad Thai]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Margarita’s Taqueria</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/mexican/2023/04/07/margaritas-taqueria.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Margarita’s Taqueria" /><published>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/mexican/2023/04/07/margaritas-taqueria</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/mexican/2023/04/07/margaritas-taqueria.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<p>Vegetarian Burrito – Pancho Villa Style</p>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Margaritas Taqueria has the best (and spiciest) vegetarian burrito we have ever had!</p>

<p>The Pancho Villa style burrito has huge Serrano peppers that provide a huge kick, help back by the coolness of chopped cucumbers and tomatoes. Finally, the orange sauce liberally spread inside provides a creamy, tangy, roasted flavor that is hard to beat. The ingredients are always fresh and the burrito assembly is always consistent.</p>

<p>Begin a food truck, the value, speed of service, and friendliness of staff is top-notch, but the ambiance isn’t that great (its placed in a parking lot with minimal seating available)</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="Mexican" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Vegetarian Burrito – Pancho Villa Style]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ramen Izakaya Yu-gen</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/ramen/2023/04/07/ramen-izakaya.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ramen Izakaya Yu-gen" /><published>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-07T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/ramen/2023/04/07/ramen-izakaya</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/ramen/2023/04/07/ramen-izakaya.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<p>Vegetable Ramen – (sub spinach noodles with normal ramen noodles)</p>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Ramen Izakaya Yu-gen has one of the best vegetarian ramens.</p>

<p>The base is vegetable broth although they have a disclaimer that they do not guarantee that the food is vegetarian. There are an assortment of free vegetables, two pieces of tofu, and an egg in the ramen so the meal ends up filling.</p>

<p>The spice level and temperature of ingredients can have some variance across experiences but the core flavor is always consistent.</p>

<p>The value and service of the food is OK compared to other places, there is a built-in gratuity and service can be slow when trying to get your check. Food service is very quick though.</p>

<p>The space is beautifully decorated and outdoor dining on Castro is always nice.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="Ramen" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Vegetable Ramen – (sub spinach noodles with normal ramen noodles)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Old Siam</title><link href="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/thai/2023/03/04/old-siam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Old Siam" /><published>2023-03-04T21:56:53+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-04T21:56:53+00:00</updated><id>http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/thai/2023/03/04/old-siam</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://anishasuharsh.com/bay%20area,%20ca/thai/2023/03/04/old-siam.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-we-ordered">What We Ordered</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Tofu Panang Curry</li>
  <li>Pad Thai</li>
  <li>Roti</li>
  <li>Tofu Basil Fried Rice</li>
  <li>Cashew Tofu Stir-fry</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="our-review">Our Review</h2>
<p>Old Siam is our favorite thai place (also very underrated). We have been coming here for years: the food is always consistent, and the all-women staff are very friendly, especially as they get to know you. Even if you only come by a couple times, they will usually remember you.</p>

<p>The spice scale goes from mild, medium, hot, and then 1 - 10 <em>after</em> hot. We usually go for a 4.</p>

<p>The Roti is nice and flaky and less oily than other thai restaurants.</p>

<p>The curries are creamy but not overly thick.</p>

<p>The pad thai is not too sweet, and super-flavorful. It might be the best pad thai.</p>

<p>Ingredients are always fresh and they are very generous in the amount of tofu and vegetables included. Portions are also large, we usually end up with leftovers for one of us the next day.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Bay Area, Ca" /><category term="Thai" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We Ordered Tofu Panang Curry Pad Thai Roti Tofu Basil Fried Rice Cashew Tofu Stir-fry]]></summary></entry></feed>